Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/tuongnguyen-phuc-cat-482691276 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Software Quality
Testing Process
Microsoft SQL Server

Tuong Nguyen Phuc Cat

Business Analyst

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I am an energetic, ambitious and hard-working person so that I'm always ready to challenge myself with new opportunities to learn more and develop myself fully.

With 2 years of experience, I am looking for a new role where I can find and challenge myself in developing software products in various domains, especially Retail \$ Ecommerce, ERP, CRM, Banking, and Finance. I aim to work with a professional team that will help me boost my skills, gain success and contribute value to the community and society.

Experience

Cadena HRM
Business Analyst
May 2024 - Present (11 months)

HD SAISON Finance Co., Ltd Software Test Engineer July 2023 - March 2024 (9 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Prepare test cases for feature improvement
- Support end-users throughout system operation
- Execute data testing in Oracle Developer, SQL Server (if required)
- Manage and report defects, change requests on the internal tracking tool
- Work closely with internal and external teams to fix defects

Digitech Solutions Co., Ltd Business Analyst September 2021 - April 2023 (1 year 8 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Gather business and system requirements from clients
- -Research relevant domain knowledge to understand features and functionalities of client's product

- Write product requirements into documents (SRS, BRD, function list, use cases, workflow,...) to review and transfer knowledge to the project team
- Report directly to Project Manager and stakeholder if required
- Create mock-up based on function list
- Manage change requirements throughout the project life cycles
- Support execute manual testing if required

Education

Truòng Dai hoc Dan Lap Van Lang
Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Management Information Systems,
General · (August 2018 - August 2022)